Raquel Spencer

Compliance and Supply Chain management up-and-comer with over 5 years of experience in Food, Fleet, and Fashion

Garden Grove, CA 92841 raquelspencer97_w3o@indeedemail.com (714) 322-8816

experience in Food, Fleet, and Fashion. Inventory Management is my primary ambition as my areas of expertise include: database management, OSHA training, and maintaining performance in high-volume-and-speed environments.

#readytowork

Work Experience

Fleet Manager

Conen's Freight Transport - Hilo, HI February 2019 to May 2020

Managed the timely renewals, maintenance, and documentation for over 70 vehicles and heavy equipment units.

- Collaborated with Shop, Accounts Payable, and the Fleet Management team to eliminate redundant charges by keeping records up to date and accurate resulting in 20% reduction in payment errors and check reissues
- · Provided all drivers with pertinent safety materials regarding rules and regulations
- Increased regulatory compliance by monitoring vehicles to verify adherence to operational, state and federal requirements specifically DOT

Compliance Specialist

Chipotle - Newport Beach, CA August 2018 to November 2018

Managed over 200 food suppliers' documentation in FoodLogic software system

- Delivered weekly performance and quality reports with data garnered from 2000+ units
- · Liaised between Logistics & Restaurant Managers concerning imminent quality issues

Digital Marketing Assistant

Vibesbase Enterprises - El Monte, CA August 2013 to August 2016

Continuously increased monthly website traffic by 30% by implementing SEO keywords in product descriptions & website copy.

· Sourced third-party content and affiliate marketers to expand social media presence

Education

Bachelor of Arts in Supply Chain Management

California State University - Fullerton, CA May 2018

Skills

- SKILLS
- OSHA Safety Training
- Microsoft Suite
- Customer Service
- Purchasing
- Bills of Lading
- Database Management
- Container Shipping
- GS1 Compliance
- LTL Freight Shipping
- Smartsheets
- Supply Chain
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- Google Analytics
- Microsoft Access